Guide to the Family planning, birth control, and sexuality publications,circa 1934-2004.
Family planning, birth control, and sexuality publications,circa 1934-1989, 2000.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Family planning, birth control, and sexuality publications, circa 1934-2004.
7326
Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County
10.2 Cubic Feet.
Manuscripts, printed materials, videotapes, films, DVDs, and tape recordings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports, conference proceedings, and books retired from Planned Parenthood's library; also audiovisual materials on contraception, menstruation, teenage pregnancy, world population, and abortion.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports, conference proceedings, and books retired from Planned Parenthood's library; also audiovisual materials on contraception, menstruation, teenage pregnancy, world population, and the 1993 New York abortion hearings; and some publications by Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County, including the 1996 Sexuality Education Center's Resource Guide and the 2000 pamphlet by Lauren R. Weinstein, "I Survived the Pap Smear and It Was Okay."
SUBJECTS
Names:
Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County
Subjects:
Birth control.; Pap test.; Sex.; Women's health.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Researchers are not to disclose names of borrowers of publications.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality.
Related collection: About Your Sexuality, #7797
Series I. Books
Box 1
Series II. Audiovisual Materials
Box 4
Series III. Publications and Subject Files
Boxes 1-2
Series IV. Educational Aids
Boxes 2-3
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Books
  - Planned Parenthood--World Population Inter-regional Statistical Report: Patient Statistics, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Planned Parenthood--World Population Inter-regional Statistical Report 1970 (Box 1)
  - Vital Statistics of New York State 1981 (Births, Deaths, Fetal Deaths, Population, Marriages, Divorces, and Trends) (Box 1)
  - 11 Million Teenagers: What Can Be Done About the Epidemic of Adolescent Pregnancies in the United States (With an afterword by Daniel Callahan), 1976 (Box 1)
  - Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention: A Team Approach (by Constance H. Shapiro in collaboration with Andrea Eggleston and Rosalind Kenworthy [professors of New York State College of Human Ecology at Cornell University]), 1979 (Box 1)
  - Vital Statistics of New York State 1980 (Births, Population, Deaths, Fetal Deaths, Divorces, Marriages) (Box 1)
  - Help For Parents: A Directory of Programs for Parents, Select Support Groups and Youth Services Available in Tompkins County (Revised May 1989) (Box 1)
  - Sex and the Teenage Girl (If it is no longer the wrong thing to do, when and with whom is it right?), 1972 (Box 1)
  - The Sexuality Education Center's Resource Guide: Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Together for Life by Joseph M. Champlin, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Contraceptive Technology 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Contraceptive Technology 1978-1979 9th Revised Edition (Box 1)
  - The Choice is Yours (U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare), 1979 (Box 1)
  - The Great Orgasm Robbery (A Book About Such Nearly-Forgotten Things in Lovemaking as Communication, Courting, Caring. Gets Beyond the Physical to the Real!!), 1981 (Box 1)
- Series II. Audiovisual Materials
  - Videos
    - "New York Abortion Hearings", V-81; 1993 copy of 16mm film, use copy (Box 4)
    - "New York Abortion Hearings", V-82; 1993 copy of 16mm film, master video copy (Box 4)
    - Sex 411, 2001; V-10088 (Box 8)
    - Leadership on International Family Planning Crisis, 1987-02; V-10089 (Box 8)
      Urgent Message from PPFA
    - One Vote Continuous Loop, 2004-07; V-10090 (Box 8)
    - Malcolm Jamal Warner PSAs, 1989-01-03; V-10091 (Box 8)
    - Bodies, Birth and Babies, 1990; V-10092 (Box 8)
    - U.S. Taxpayers Party of Wisconsin-State Convention, 1994-05-27-1994-05-28; V-10093 (Box 8)
    - Smith Greenland, NYS Family Planning, Media Consortium, 1987-05-28; V-10094 (Box 8)
    - Silent Scream, Date Unknown; V-10095 (Box 8)
    - Radiant Rebel, Date Unknown; V-10096 (Box 8)
    - Women Vote 2004, The Margin of Victory, 2004; V-10097 (Box 8)
    - 30th Anniversary Roe v. Wade, 2003-03; V-10098 (Box 8)
    - The Struggle for Birth Control: A Historical Perspective, Date Unknown; V-10099 (Box 8)
    - Counselor, Becky Bell, Home, Phone Booth, Why, Date Unknown; V-10100 (Box 8)
    - PPTC Staff Orientation, Date Unknown; V-10101 (Box 8)
    - PPTC 20th Anniv., Sarah Weddington, 1988-05-09; V-10102 (Box 8)
    - Planned Parenthood, Emerson Suites, Ithaca College, 1993-05-09; V-10103 (Box 8)
    - Abortion Ban Signing News Coverage, 2003-10-2003-11; V-10104 (Box 8)
      Planned Parenthood Gets The Message Through
    - The 1989 March for Women's Equality/Women's Lives, 1989-04-09; V-10105 (Box 8)
    - One-Woman Powerful Women Performances with Miriam Reed as Elizabeth Cady Stanton and Susan B. Anthony, 1996-08; V-10106 (Box 8)
    - PPTC Annual Meeting, 1999-05-24; V-10107 (Box 8)
    - Presentation of the Constance E. Cook Community Service Award to Libby McLellan, 2003-05-12; V-10108 (Box 8)
    - Access Denied, Date Unknown; V-10109 (Box 8)
      U.S. Restrictions on International Family Planning, Global Gag Rule Impact Project
    - PPTC Annual Meeting, 1991; V-10110 (Box 8)
    - Women Vote 2004, The Margin of Victory, 2004; V-10111 (Box 8)
    - America at a Crossroads, 1990; V-10112 (Box 8)
    - One-Woman Powerful Women Performances with Miriam Reed as Elizabeth Cady Stanton and Susan B. Anthony, 1996-08; V-10113 (Box 8)
    - Date Unknown, V-10114 (Box 8)
    - PP Global Partners "Dream", Television and Radio, Date Unknown; V-10115 (Box 8)
    - Al Moran Speech, Date Unknown; V-10116 (Box 8)
      No open or close, Pro Unit Ithaca College
    - Garrity Communications, Inc., Date Unknown; V-10117 (Box 8)
    - CROSSING BORDERS: Sexual Reproductive Health in Namibia, 2004; V-10118 (Box 8)
    - We Care, Date Unknown; V-10119 (Box 8)
    - PPTC Staff Interviews "Original", 1987; V-10120 (Box 8)
    - PPTC 25th Ann. Video, Interviews #1, Date Unknown; V-10121 (Box 8)
    - What Do I Know About Me?, 2000-11-08; V-10122 (Box 8)
      English and Spanish
    - Skateboard/Surfer Girl, Basketball/Car, Skateboard/Basketball, 2000-05-16; V-10123 (Box 8)
      VOX/800-230-PLAN, RC/800-230-PLAN
    - Cancel The Debt Now!, 2000; V-10124 (Box 8)
    - 1989-04-01, V-10125 (Box 8)
    - When Abortion Was Illegal: Untold Stories, 1992; V-10126 (Box 9)
    - A Conversation with Brian McNaught On Being Gay, 1986; V-10127 (Box 9)
    - Speaking For Ourselves, Date Unknown; V-10128 (Box 9)
      Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Youths
    - Planned Parenthood US Contraceptive, 1987-04-21; V-10129 (Box 9)
    - Griswold V. Connecticut, 1995-06-07; V-10130 (Box 9)
      30 Anniversary VNH
    - PPFA: Roe vs. Wade, Date Unknown; V-10131 (Box 9)
    - Matthew Broderick P.S.A.'s for National Family Sexuality Education Month, Date Unknown; V-10132 (Box 9)
    - Press Conference to Announce PPFA's New President Gloria A. Feldt, 1996-04-23; V-10133 (Box 9)
    - Video Press Backgrounder of Anti-Choice Movement, 1989-03-17; V-10134 (Box 9)
    - "Becky Bell/Vers. A " :30 Spot, Date Unknown; V-10135 (Box 9)
      "A Mother's Tear"-Becky Bell 20:00
    - Unholy Alliance, 1995; V-10136 (Box 9)
    - From Danger To Dignity, 1995; V-10137 (Box 9)
      The Fight for Safe Abortion
    - Off the Straight and Narrow, 1998; V-10138 (Box 9)
      Lesbians, Gays, Bisexuals, and Television
    - PP Response to the Silent Scream - Long Version, Date Unknown; V-10139 (Box 9)
    - It's Up To You - Teen Pregnancy in Hawaii, Date Unknown; V-10140 (Box 9)
    - Common Counsil Resolution, Date Unknown; V-10141 (Box 9)
    - Channel 7 Coverage of Picketers, 1994-04-08; V-10142 (Box 9)
    - WENY Broadcast, 1997-10-19; V-10143 (Box 9)
      Penni, Bob Marge "Two Women…"
    - PPIC 25TH Ann. Video, Date Unknown; V-10144 (Box 9)
      Interviews - #2
    - Raw footage of Planned Parenthood Anniversary, 1988-05-09; V-10145 (Box 9)
      Cable NewsCenter7, News Conference
    - Supremes for Choice Rally, 1992-07; V-10146 (Box 9)
      25th Anniversary Video
    - The Struggle for Birth Control; A Historical Perspective, Date Unknown; V-10147 (Box 9)
    - PPTC in the News CN-7, V-10148 (Box 9)
    - The Days are So Long, Date Unknown; V-10149 (Box 9)
      Can Love Cry?, I Can't Imagine, Amanda, It is Me and You
    - Namibia, Date Unknown; V-10150 (Box 9)
      Katatura Comm. Radio, Billboards, Moria Grace, Was Fashion Show
    - Be True To Yourself, 1991; V-10151 (Box 9)
      Bob and Rod Jackson - Paris, Talk with Ten Teenagers
    - Becky's Story, 1991-02-24; V-10152 (Box 9)
      CBS News, 60 Minutes
    - In a Just World: Abortion, Contraception, and World Religion, Date Unknown; V-10153 (Box 9)
    - Public hearing on abortion funding resolution, Date Unknown; V-10154 (Box 9)
    - PPST Annual Luncheon w/ Shirley Gordon, Date Unknown; V-10155 (Box 9)
    - Fashion Show Footage, 1993; V-10156 (Box 9)
    - Gay Pioneers, 1965-06-04; V-10157 (Box 9)
    - Interviews w/ PPTL staff on Public Affairs Program, 1989-05; V-10158 (Box 9)
    - A Friend of the Family for Twenty Years, Date Unknown; V-10159 (Box 9)
    - Voices for Choice, Voices for Peace Rally, 1998-10-29; V-10160 (Box 9)
    - One-Woman Powerful Women Performances with Miriam Reed as Elizabeth Cady Stanton and Susan B. Anthony, 1999; V-10161 (Box 10)
    - Life in the womb, 2000-09-11; V-10162 (Box 10)
      Roy K. retirement party, [Another title that is indecipherable]
    - Libby McLellan Interview, Date Unknown; V-10163 (Box 10)
    - Murder on Abortion Row, Date Unknown; V-10164 (Box 10)
    - What Do I Know About Me?, 2001-04-17; V-10165 (Box 10)
    - Sterilization Project - "La-Operation", Date Unknown; V-10166; Betacam (Box 10)
    - The Body Human, Date Unknown; V-10167 (Box 10)
      Facts for Boys
    - The March on Washington, 1989-04-09; V-10168 (Box 10)
      Post-Webster Remarks
    - Mom/Vote, 1996-08-02; V-10169 (Box 10)
    - Educate and Advocate Options Counseling and the Gag Rule", 1991-03-19; V-10170 (Box 10)
    - Kathleen Turner PSA's for Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc.'s, 1993-07-20; V-10171 (Box 10)
    - PPTC TV Interviews, Date Unknown; V-10172 (Box 10)
    - Board Meeting on Primary Care, 1994-02-22; V-10173 (Box 10)
    - Planned parenthood of Tom County Interviews, 1988-02-10; V-10174 (Box 10)
      Evans, Cook, Bandler, Miller
    - Music Collage, Date Unknown; V-10175 (Box 10)
      Madana Peep Show, Touch Me, Gone w/ the Wind, Down and Out, Pillow Talk, Kris Kristuffar, LA Law, Daddy, Pappa Don't Preach
    - Human Sexual Response, Date Unknown; V-10176 (Box 10)
    - No Money, Basics, Ball, Date Unknown; V-10177 (Box 10)
    - A Friend of the Family for 20 years, Date Unknown; V-10178 (Box 10)
    - Planned Parenthood Interviews Dr and Mrs Ley, Sue Kilgor, Roz Kenworth, Date Unknown; V-10179 (Box 10)
    - We Care, 1992-11-04; V-10180 (Box 10)
    - Parent - Child Coummunication PSAs, 1997; V-10181 (Box 10)
      Swoosie Kurtz
    - Leslie, Townsend, Kennedy, Potteiger, Date Unknown; V-10182 (Box 10)
    - PPTC Constance E. Cook Award, 2003; V-10183; Mini DV (Box 10)
      Elizabeth McLellan
    - Campaign to Promote Family Planning and Planned Parenthood Services, 1997-04-15; V-10184; Betacam (Box 10)
      Family 1, Family 2
    - New York Abortion Hearings, Date Unknown; V-10185 (Box 10)
    - Cook Cohen Tape, Date Unknown; V-10186 (Box 10)
    - Talking Tough Issues, 1990; V-10187 (Box 10)
      Annual Meeting
    - Teen Pregnancy Television Series, Date Unknown; V-10188 (Box 11)
      1) Father, 2) Mother, 3) Older Brother, 4) Should Have Said #1, 5) Son, 6) Should Have Said #2, 7) Older Sister, 8) Cute, 9) Birth Control
    - Talk To Me, Date Unknown; V-10189 (Box 11)
      Growing Up Begins at Home
    - N.Y.S. Family Planning Media Consortium, 1987-08-20; V-10190 (Box 11)
      A) NYC/English, B) NYC/Spanish, C) Buffalo/English, D) Buffalo/Spanish
    - Condoms for Disease Control (awareness), 1987-06; V-10191 (Box 11)
    - On Hostile Ground, 2000; V-10192 (Box 11)
      The stories of three abortion providers
    - United Nations Population Fund, 1999-04; V-10193 (Box 11)
      Adolescence / Gender Equality
    - World Population, 2000; V-10194 (Box 11)
      A Graphic Simulatin of the History of Human Population Growth
    - Yes, You Can Ask for a Gift, Date Unknown; V-10195 (Box 11)
    - America Today, 1993-11-23; V-10196 (Box 11)
    - "Condom," "Loud Speaker," "Hockey," "Sneeze," "Sperm," "Baby, Baby", 1997-07-22; V-10197 (Box 11)
    - Family Communication, 1991-08-12; V-10198 (Box 11)
      Judy Blume
    - Whose Choice?, Date Unknown; V-10199 (Box 11)
    - I Witness, Date Unknown; V-10200 (Box 11)
    - Power the Promise, 2004-03-19; V-10201 (Box 11)
      Leadership Council Video
    - Live Free or Die, Date Unknown; V-10202 (Box 11)
    - Abortion for Survival, Date Unknown; V-10203 (Box 11)
    - Coming to Say Goodbye (Stories of AIDS in Africa), 2002; V-10204 (Box 11)
    - Life, Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness, Date Unknown; V-10205 (Box 11)
      It's About Everything and One Thing - Choice
    - Farewell Party for Kate Potteiger, 1990-07; V-10206 (Box 11)
    - Planned Parenthood - Mitchell, Ward, Berllofer, Date Unknown; V-10207 (Box 11)
    - Planned Parenthood on TV, 1999-11-23-2000-06-28; V-10208 (Box 11)
      Dated: 11/23/99, 1/7/00, 2/15/00, 2/14/00, 4/25/00, 6/28/00
    - PPTC - TV News (Cable 7), Date Unknown; V-10209 (Box 11)
    - Planned Parenthood Interviews, Date Unknown; V-10210 (Box 11)
      Levitt, Hill, Ferger, Holmberg, Connor
    - Faces of Pro-Choice America, 1992-10-22; V-10211 (Box 11)
    - Fundamental Rights Abortion, Date Unknown; V-10212 (Box 11)
      1. PA Abortion Control Act 2. When Ab was Illegal
    - Planned Parenthood Interviews, Date Unknown; V-10213 (Box 11)
      Bixler, Gortzig | Robert R. Julian Media-Message Communications
    - Best Wishes, 1993-05-19; V-10214 (Box 11)
    - PPTC Annual Meeting, 1992-05; V-10215 (Box 11)
    - The Talk, Date Unknown; V-10216 (Box 11)
      Planned Parenthood Public Service Announcement
  - Films
    - Cindy and Jack, 1977; F-2111 (Box 4)
    - "Ginger", F-2112; 16mm film (Box 4)
      Teenage girl has just found out she's pregnant; tries to talk with a friend. Neither knows what to do
    - New York Abortion Hearings, F-2113; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - Menstruation, 1976; F-2114; 16mm film, 18 minutes (Box 4)
    - Teenage Pregnancy #2, F-2115; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - "Something Very Special", F-2116 (Box 4)
    - "Your Pelvic and Breast Exam", F-2117 (Box 4)
    - Five Million, F-2118 (Box 4)
    - Planned Families #2 (The use of vaginal sponges, suppositories, and foaming vaginal tablets is no longer recommended. There are more effective methods available today), F-2119; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - Hope is Not a Method-II, F-2120 (Box 4)
    - Teen Sexuality, 1976; F-2121 (Box 4)
    - Assorted film strips from "About Your Sexuality" kit, Circa 1983-1989 (Box 4)
    - "You're Having My Baby", F-2122; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - "It's Common Knowledge", F-2123; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - "Mark and Susan - Parking Scene", F-2124; 16mm film (Box 4)
    - "Gretchen", F-2125; 16mm film (Box 4)
      Teen mother talking with another girl
    - A Family Talks About Sex, 1979-03; F-2068 (Box 5)
    - Teenage Father, Date Unknown; F-2069 (Box 5)
    - Another Half, Date Unknown; F-2070 (Box 5)
    - Dear Diary, Date Unknown; F-2071 (Box 5)
    - Loving Parents, Date Unknown; F-2072 (Box 5)
    - Heroes and Strangers, Date Unknown; F-2073 (Box 5)
    - Are You Ready For Sex, Date Unknown; F-2074 (Box 5)
    - A Far Cry From Yesterday, Date Unknown; F-2075 (Box 5)
    - Just One of the Boys, Date Unknown; F-2076 (Box 5)
    - Lucy: A Teenage Pregnancy, Date Unknown; F-2077 (Box 5)
    - The Date, Date Unknown; F-2078 (Box 5)
    - Making Points, Date Unknown; F-2079 (Box 6)
    - Party Game, Date Unknown; F-2080 (Box 6)
    - End of the Road, Date Unknown; F-2081 (Box 6)
    - Popcorn, Date Unknown; F-2082 (Box 6)
    - Doin' What the Crowd Does, Date Unknown; F-2083 (Box 6)
    - The Teachers, Date Unknown; F-2084 (Box 6)
      Parent Child Communications Campaign
    - Waiting Room, Date Unknown; F-2085 (Box 6)
    - Saying No, Date Unknown; F-2086 (Box 6)
    - Messages, Date Unknown; F-2087 (Box 6)
    - About Sex, Date Unknown; F-2088 (Box 6)
    - Four Young Women, Date Unknown; F-2089 (Box 6)
    - Hope is Not a Method - Part II, Date Unknown; F-2090 (Box 6)
    - Adolescent Sexual Conflict: Are We Still Going to the Movies?, 1974; F-2091 (Box 6)
    - Running My Way, Date Unknown; F-2092 (Box 6)
    - Condom Sense, Date Unknown; F-2093 (Box 6)
    - The Choice is Yours, Date Unknown; F-2094 (Box 6)
    - Birth Control Movie, Date Unknown; F-2095 (Box 6)
    - Am I Normal, Date Unknown; F-2096 (Box 7)
    - Human Growth IV, Date Unknown; F-2097 (Box 7)
    - Would You Kiss a Naked Man, 1982; F-2098 (Box 7)
    - Trying Time, Date Unknown; F-2099 (Box 7)
    - Your Pelvic and Breast Exam, Date Unknown; F-2100 (Box 7)
    - Old Bugs New Problems, Date Unknown; F-2101 (Box 7)
    - Vasectomy, Date Unknown; F-2102 (Box 7)
    - The Touch Film, Date Unknown; F-2103 (Box 7)
    - Sex, Drugs and AIDS, Date Unknown; F-2104 (Box 7)
    - Belly Buttons are Navels, Date Unknown; F-2105 (Box 7)
    - A Tender Balance, Date Unknown; F-2106 (Box 7)
    - In Between, Date Unknown; F-2107 (Box 7)
    - What Tadoo, Date Unknown; F-2108 (Box 7)
    - Happy Little Hamsters, Date Unknown; F-2109 (Box 7)
      Third Edition
    - Personal Decisions, Date Unknown; F-2110
  - DVDs and Tape recordings
    - Crossing Boarders: Sexual Reproductive Health in Namibia, 2004; DVD-2378 (type="box">10)
    - The Power of Choice, Date Unknown; DVD-2376 (type="box">10)
    - Access Denied, Date Unknown; DVD-2377 (type="box">10)
      U.S. Restrictions on International Family Planning
    - Population-- Planned Parenthood World Population-- Talk, TR-11557 (Box 4)
    - Loneliness by accident, Date Unknown; TR-16022 (type="box">10)
      4 out of 5 young, Birth Control, You're too smart not to use it, has old [indecipherable] for put an cassette for us?
- Series III. Publications and Subject Files
  - "Family Planner", January/February 1970-Spring 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Family Planning Digest" volume 1 (1) January 1972- volume 2 (6) November 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Family Planning Digest" volume 3 (1) January 1974- volume 3 (7) January 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Family Planning/ Population Reporter" volume 2 (1) February 1973- volume 3 (2) April 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Family Planning/ Population Reporter" volume 3 (3) June 1974-volume 4 (5) October 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Family Planning/ Population Reporter" volume 4 (6) December 1975-volume 6 (3) June 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Family Planning/ Population Reporter" volume 6 (4) August 1977- volume 8 (3) June 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Family Planning/ Population Reporter" volume 8 (4) August 1979- volume 10 (3) June 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Getting It Together", circa 1970-August 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Sex News", October 1974-March 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Sex News", April 1978-October 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "SIECUS Newsletter", October 1968- April 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "SIECUS Report", September 1972-July 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "SIECUS Report", March 1979- November 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lauren R. Weinstein, "I Survived the Pap Smear and It Was Okay.", 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ithaca College dorm program, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University correspondence, 1970-1973, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Planned Parenthood pamphlets and event flyers (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Resources for parents and educators on sex education for adolescents (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Venereal disease (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - United States population (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Research on Black Sexuality: A Selected Bibliography", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County correspondence and education department files, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Your Guide to the: Sexuality Education Resource Center. Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fertility Awareness. Counselor/Educator's Manual. By Patricia A. Coury, Barbara Ochester and the Fertility Awareness Project of Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "3Rs" newsletters, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Pregnant Too Soon Study Guide Answer Key, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - AIDS Education File: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Second Report on Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices (The Medical Device and Drug Advisory Committees on Obstetrics and Gynecology), December 1978 (Box 2)
  - Abortion: Need, Services and Policies New York, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Provisional Estimates of Abortion Need and Services In the Year Following the 1973 Supreme Court Decisions United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Abortion 1976-1977 Need and Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Abortion 1977-1979 Need and Services in the United States, Each State and Metropolitan Area, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses For 1976 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan For Family Planning Services, September 1976 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses For 1975 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan For Family Planning Services, May 1975 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses for 1973 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services (Box 2)
  - World Population Growth and Response 1965-1975- a decade of global action (Box 2)
  - Family Planning: An Analysis Of Laws and Policies in the United States, September 1971 (Box 2)
  - Fertility Related Services in the HSA: Need Assessment and Current Service Levels, March 1978 (Box 2)
  - Five-Year Plan for Family Planning Services and Population Research, September 1979 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses for 1978 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan For Family Planning Services, December 1979 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses for a State Plan for Family Planning Services in Upstate New York Volume 1, February 1974 (Box 2)
  - Data and Analyses for 1977 Revision of DHEW Five-Year Plan For Family Planning Services, December 1977 (Box 2)
  - Proceedings of the National Family Planning Forum, October 4-6, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Need for Subsidized Family Planning Services: United States, Each State and County, 1969. (Box 2)
  - Proceedings of the National Conference on the Delivery of Family Planning Services in Rural America, October 5-7, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Population and Family Planning Programs A compendium of data through 1978 by Dorothy L. Norman and Ellen Hofstatter, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Organized Family Planning Services in the United States, 1981-1983, December 1984 (Box 2)
  - The Lalor Foundation, Sixth Edition of UTERINE ASPIRATION PROCEDURES, June 1971 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Family Planning International Assistance), 1971 (Box 2)
  - Directory of Family Planning Grantees and Clinics, July 1979 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Marrying, Divorcing, and Living Together in the U.S. Today, October 1977 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: The Elderly In America, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: World Population Projections: Alternative Paths to Zero Growth, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: The Value and Cost of Children, April 1977 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Epidemiologic Transition in the U.S., May 1977 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Rural Renaissance in America?, October 1976 (Box 2)